Theatre, Department of; Records ua609
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Production Files, 1953-1985; 2; 1 cubic foot
  - American Hurrah, 1968 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 3)
  - The Beautiful People, 1962 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 4)
  - Biederman and the Firebugs, 1963 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 5)
  - Big, Soft Nellie, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 6)
  - The Birthday Party, 1971 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 7)
  - The Book of Job, 1970 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 8)
  - Calling of Mother Ann, 1985 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 9)
  - Camino Real, 1970 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 10)
  - The Cave Dwellers, 1959 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 11)
  - A Chekhov Afternoon, 1971 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 12)
  - Comedy of Errors, 1974 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 13)
  - The Contrast, 1959 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 14)
  - The Crucible, 1956 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 15)
  - Dark of the Moon, 1975 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 16)
  - Diary of a Scoundrel, 1956 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 17)
  - Dr. Knock, 1956 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 18)
  - Everyman, 1963 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 19)
  - Exit the King/The Misanthrope, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 20)
  - Exit the King, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 21)
  - Fairytales of New York, 1961-1963 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 22)
  - Fairytales of New York, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 23)
  - Ghosts, 1962 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 24)
  - Girls in Uniform, 1954-1955 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 25)
  - Girls in Uniform, 1955 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 26)
  - Great American Light War, 1972 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 27)
  - Harry, Noon, and Night, 1970 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 28)
  - Henry IV, 1971 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 29)
  - The Iceman Cometh, 1960 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 30)
  - The Imaginary Invalid, 1960 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 31)
  - The Imaginary Invalid, 1975 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 32)
  - The Insect Comedy, 1957 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 33)
  - An Italian Straw Hat, 1960 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 34)
  - Jezebel's Husband, 1953 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 35)
  - Laburnum Grove, 1955 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 36)
  - Lamp at Midnight, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 37)
  - Legend of Lovers, 1959 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 38)
  - The Little Mahoghany, 1975 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 39)
  - The Living Room, 1957 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 40)
  - Macbeth, 1956 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 41)
  - Mandragola, 1961 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 42)
  - Marigolds, 1975 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 43)
  - The Marriage, 1958 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 44)
  - Martine, 1961-1962 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 45)
  - Measures Taken and Bald Soprano, 1971 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 46)
  - The Moon is Blue, 1953 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 47)
  - Moonchildren, 1975 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 48)
  - Mother Courage, 1955 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 49)
  - Murder in the Cathedral, 1962 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 50)
  - Night of the Auk, 1959-1963 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 51)
  - Oedipus Rex, 1961 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 52)
  - Orestes, 1970 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 53)
  - Othello, 1956-1961 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 54)
  - Parades, 1961 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 55)
  - Peter Pan, 1971 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 56)
  - The Playboy of the Western World, 1962 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 57)
  - The Pride of the Claghorne, Undated (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 58)
  - The Queen and the Rebels, 1960 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 59)
  - Red Eye of Love, 1963 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 60)
  - Reprieve for the World, 1960 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 61)
  - Ring Around the World, 1961 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 62)
  - Rip Van Winkle, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 63)
  - Royal Gambit, 1966 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 64)
  - Royal Hunt of the Sun, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 65)
  - A Scent of Flowers, 1970 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 66)
  - The Skin of Our Teeth, 1968 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 67)
  - Slow Dance on the Killing Ground, 1965 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 68)
  - Song of a Goat, 1971 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 69)
  - Step in the Hollow, 1961 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 70)
  - Summertime, 1958 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 71)
  - Tiger at the Gates, 1958 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 72)
  - Troillus and Cressida, 1972 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 73)
  - The Trojan Women, 1953 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 74)
  - Twelve Angry Men, 1960 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 75)
  - Uncle Vanya/ The Cherry Orchard, 1959 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 76)
  - University Theatre Productions, 1964-1981 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 77)
  - University Theatre Productions, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 78)
  - Waiting for Godot, 1956 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 79)
  - Waiting for Godot, 1975; 2 folders (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 80-81)
  - Wilbur the Giant, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 82)
  - The Wizard of Oz, 1974 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 83)
  - The Yellow Laugh, 1971 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 84)
  - Your Own Thing, 1970 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 85)
  - Zone, 1970 (Box 1 (2-Production Files), Folder 86)
- Appendix: Theatre Productions Directed by Faculty, 1956-1996; 3
  List includes: Date, Last Name of the Author, Title of Production, Last Name of Faculty Member, and Location of Production.
  - Ostrovsky, Diary of a Scoundrel, Burian, Page, 1956 January
  - Shakespeare, Macbeth, Pettit, Page, 1956 April
  - Howard, They Knew What They Wanted, Pettit, Page, 1956 Summer
  - Anouilh, Thieves' Carnival, Smith, Page Arena, 1956 Summer
  - Beckett, Waiting for Godot, Pettit, Page Arena, 1956 Summer
  - Romains, Dr. Knock, Pettit, Page, 1956 November
  - Capek, Insect Comedy, Burian, Page, 1957 March
  - Sopholes, Antigone, Leonard, Page, 1957 May
  - Molnar, Play's the Thing, Pettit, Page Arena, 1957 Summer
  - Greene, Living Room, Smith, Page Arena, 1957 Summer
  - Obler, Night of the Auk, Pettit, Page Arena, 1957 Summer
  - Miller, View from the Bridge, Burian, Page, 1957 November
  - Gogol, Marrigae, Leonard, Page (New Paltz), 1958 May
  - Betti, Summertime, Pettit, Page Arena, 1958 Summer
  - Hellman, Children's Hour, Smith, Page Arena, 1958 Summer
  - Boland, Prisoner, Pettit, Page Arena, 1958 Summer
  - Giraudoux, Tiger at the Gates, Burian, Page, 1958 November
  - Tyler, Contrast, Harper, Richardson 291, 1959 February
  - Anouilh, Legend of Lovers, Pettit, Page, 1959 May
  - Shaw, Too True to Be Good, Burian, Page Arena, 1959 Summer
  - Lorca House of Bernarda Alba, Dace, Page Arena, 1959 Summer
  - Chekhov, Uncle Vanya, Burian, Page Arena, 1959 Summer
  - Saroyan, Cave Dwellers, Leonard, Page, 1959 November
  - Betti, Queen and the Rebels, Burian, Richardson 291, 1960 February
  - Labiche, Italian Straw Hat, Pettit, Page, 1960 May
  - Rose, Twelve Angry Men, Leonard, Page Arena, 1960 Summer
  - Perl, Tevya and His Daughters, Smith, Page Arena, 1960 Summer
  - Sternheim, Snob, Pettit, Page Arena, 1960 Summer
  - O'Neill, Iceman Cometh, Burian, Page (Cornell), 1960 November
  - Anouilh, Ring Round the Moon, Leonard, Richardson 291, 1961 February
  - Sophocles, Oedipus the King, Pettit, Page, 1961 May
  - Machiavelli, Mandragola, Pettit, Page Arena, 1961 Summer
  - MacDonagh, Step in the Hollow, Leonard, Page Arena, 1961 Summer
  - Brecht, Drums in the Night, Pettit, Page Arena, 1961 Summer
  - Shakespeare, Othello, Swearingen, Page, 1961 November
  - Ibsen, Ghosts, Leonard, Richardson 291, 1962 February
  - Saroyan, Beautiful People, Manaus, Page, 1962 May
  - Donleavy, Fairy Tales of New York, Pettit, Page Arena, 1962 Summer
  - Simpson, Resounding Tinkle, Leonard, Page Arena, 1962 Summer
  - Mortimer, Dock Brief, Leonard, Page Arena, 1962 Summer
  - Bernard, Martine, Pettit, Page Arena, 1962 Summer
  - Eliot, Murder in the Cathedral, Burian, All Saints, 1962 November
  - Synge, Playboy Western World, Mendez, Richardson 291, 1962 December
  - Genet, Maids, Burian, Richardson 291, 1963 February
  - Johnson, What Did You Learn..., Burian, Richardson 291, 1963 February
  - Weinstein, Red Eye of Love, Leonard, Page, 1963 May
  - O'Neill, Emperor Jones, Burian, Page Arena, 1963 Summer
  - Frisch, Biederwann and the Firebugs, Smith, Page Arena, 1963 Summer
  - Chekhov, Three Sisters, Burian, Page Arena, 1963 Summer
  - Brecht, Good Woman of Setzuan, Burian, Leonard, Page, 1963 November
  - Dos Passos, U.S.A., Leonard, Richardson 291, 1963 December
  - Sartre, Flies, Mendus, Richardson 291, 1964 February
  - Kaiser, Raft of the Medusa, Leonard, Page, 1964 May
  - Shakespeare, The Tempest, Burian, Page Arena, 1964 Summer
  - Goldoni, Mistress of the Inn, Smith, Page Arena, 1964 Summer
  - Strindberg, Ghost Sonata, Burian, Page Arena, 1964 Summer
  - Marlowe, Doctor Faustus, Burian, All Saints, 1964 November
  - Schisgal, Typists and Tiger, Leonard, Richardson 291, 1964 December
  - Wharton, Ethan Frome, Pettit, Richardson 291, 1965 February
  - Moliere, Misanthrope, Leonard, Page, 1965 May
  - Hanley, Slow Dance on the Killing Ground, Yeaton, Page Arena, 1965 Summer
  - Saroyan, Jim Dandy, Smith, Page Arena, 1965 Summer
  - Jonson, Alchemist, Yeaton, Page Arena, 1965 Summer
  - Steinbeck, Of Mice and Men, Leonard, Page, 1965 November
  - Cheever, Wapshot Scandal, Stephen, Richardson 291, 1965 December
  - Newley, Stop the World, Mann, Richardson 291, 1966 February
  - MacLeish, J.B., Burian, Trinity Methodist, 1966 April
  - Kennelly, Special Assignment, Leonard, Page Arena, 1966 Summer
  - Brener, Regatta, Leonard, Page Arena, 1966 Summer
  - Gurney, Rape of Bunny Stuntz, Leonard, Page Arena, 1966 Summer
  - Bernard, Springtime of Others, Pettit, Page Arena, 1966 Summer
  - Pinter, Birthday Party, Burian, Page Arena, 1966 Summer
  - Aristophanes, Lysistrata, Pettit, Page (Buffalo), 1966 November
  - Havel, Memorandum, Burian, Richardson 291, 1966 December
  - Kaufman, Merton of the Movies, Leonard, Page, 1967 March
  - Laurents, Clearing in the Woods, Mann, Lakeside Thr, 1967 April
  - Chekhov, Sea Gull, Stirlen, Page Arena, 1967 Summer
  - Jellicoe, Knack, Velie, Page Arena, 1967 Summer
  - Shaw, Widower's Houses, Leonard, Page Arena, 1967 Summer
  - O'Neill, Highie, Burian, Page Arena, 1967 Summer
  - Pincer, Dumbwaiter, Burian, Page Arena, 1967 Summer
  - Brecht, Private Life Master Race, Leonard, Page, 1967 November
  - Rice, Adding Machine, Mann, Hawley Library, 1967 December
  - Sehnitzler, Affairs of Anatol, Pettit, Richardson 291, 1968 March
  - Shakespeare, Hamlet, Ql, Burian, Page, 1968 May
  - Shepard, Red Cross, Velie, Richardson 291, 1968 Summer
  - Mrozek, Out at Sea, Velie, Richardson 291, 1968 Summer
  - Bond, King and the Subject, Atkinson, Richardson 291, 1968 Summer
  - Anouilh, Stimulus the Mute, Atkinson, Richardson 291, 1968 Summer
  - Beckett, Endgame, Irian, Richardson 291, 1968 Summer
  - Donleavy, Fairy Tales of New York, Pettit, Richardson 291, 1968 November
  - Livings, Big Soft Melly, Leonard, Arena, 1968 December
  - Harris, Androcles and the Lion, Snyder, Richardson 291, 1969 April
  - Wilder, Skin of Our Teeth, Mann, Studio, 1969 May
  - Hamilton, Angel Street, Mann, Studio, 1969 Summer
  - Vos, Prof. Filarskey's..., Snyder, Lab, 1969 Summer
  - Osborne, Entertainer, Velie, Studio, 1969 Summer
  - Beckett, Acts Without Words, Smith, Lab, 1969 Summer
  - Lennon, In His Own Write, Smith, Lab, 1969 Summer
  - Shaffer, Royal Hunt of the Sun, Pettit, Main, 1969 November
  - Jefferson, Rip Van Winkle, Mendus, Lab, 1969 December
  - Pettit, Ala-Ed-Din, Snyder, Lab, 1969 December
  - Euripides, Orestes, Weiner, Main, 1970 February
  - Driver, Your Own Thing, Balfior, Studio, 1970 May
  - Williams, Camino Real, Balfior, Main, 1970 October
  - Saunders, Scent of Flowers Burian, Lab, 1970 November
  - Ribkin, Harry, Noon and Night, Weiner, Studio, 1970 December
  - Barrie, Peter Pan, Snyder, Main, 1971 March
  - Brecht, Measures Taken, Burian, Lab, 1971 April
  - Ionesco, Bald Soprano, Balfior, Studio, 1971 April
  - Johnson, Great American Light War, Leonard, Page, 1971 October
  - Pirandello, Henry IV, Sogliuzzo, Studio, 1971 November
  - Shakespeare, Troilus and Cressida, Sugarman, Lab, 1972 April
  - Littlewood, Oh, What a Lovely War, Sugarman, Main, 1972 Summer
  - Kafka, Trial, Atkinson, Arena, 1972 Summer
  - Stein, Gertrude Stein's Fret Rder, Snyder, Studio, 1972 Fall
  - Weiss, Marat Sade, Burian, Main, 1972 November
  - Richardson, Gallow's' s Humor, Leonard, Studio, 1972 November
  - LeGallienne, Alice in Wonderland, Snyder, Arena, 1972 December
  - Shaw, Arms and the Man, Mendus, Studio, 1973 February
  - Katz, Three Cuckolds, Sogliuzzo, Lab, 1973 Spring
  - Howard, Most Happy Fella, Balfior, Main, 1973 May
  - Chekhov, Cherry Orchard, Burian, Main, 1973 Summer
  - Pirandello, Six Characters in Search of an Author, Atkinson, Studio, 1973 Summer
  - O'Neill et. al., Fathers and Sons, Burian, Arena, 1973 Summer
  - Strindberg, Mothereoven, Atkinson, Arena, 1973 Summer
  - Schiller, Maria Stuart, Weiner, Main, 1973 October
  - Baum, Wizard of Oz, Snyder, Studio, 1973 December
  - Sophocles, Oedipus-Antigone, Burian, Studio, 1974 February
  - Shakespeare, Comedy of Errors, Golden, Main, 1974 March
  - Kopit, Oh Dad, Poor Dad, Hanley, Studio, 1974 May
  - Masters, Spoon River, Golden, Lab, 1974 Summer
  - Guare, House of Blue Leaves, Weiner, Lab, 1974 Summer
  - Wilson, Rimers of Eldritch, Hartley, Lab, 1974 October
  - Feydeau Flea in Her Ear, Weiner, Main, 1974 December
  - Richardson, Dark of the Moan, Golden, Main, 1975 March
  - Moliere, Imaginary Invalid, Symons, Lab, 1975 May
  - Smith, Drunkard, Golden, Lab, 1975 Summer
  - de Hartog, Four Poster, Symons, Arena, 1975 Summer
  - Albee, Who's Afraid Virginia Woolf?, Poppick, Studio, 1975 Summer
  - Wilder, Our Town, Golden, Lab, 1975 Summer
  - Beckett, Waiting for Godot, Symons, Main, 1975 October
  - Zindel, Gamma Rays, Leonard, Studio, 1975 October
  - Weller, Moonchildren, Golden, Main, 1975 November
  - Gibson, American Primitive, Hanley, Main, 1976 February
  - Euripides, Medea, Mendus, Arena, 1976 March
  - Synge, The Playboy of the Western World, Golden, Main, 1976 April
  - Rinehart, Bat, Golden, Lab, 1976 Summer
  - Shakespeare, Midsummer Night's Dream, Symons, Main, 1976 Summer
  - Coward, Hay Fever, Golden, Studio, 1976 Summer
  - Shelley/Kelly, Frankenstein, Leonard, Main, 1976 October
  - Pinter, Old Times, Burian, Main (arena), 1976 November
  - Chekhov, Uncle Vanya, Symons, Lab, 1976 December
  - Durenmatt, Biedermann and the Firebugs, Symons, Lab, 1976 December
  - Orton, What the Butler Saw, Weiner, Studio, 1977 March
  - Farquar, Beaux Stratagem, Golden, Main, 1977 April
  - Hailey, Who's Happy Now?, Hanley, Studio, 1977 May
  - Wilson, Hot 1 Baltimore, Golden, Main (arena), 1977 Summer
  - McNally, Bad Habits, Hanley, Lab, 1977 Summer
  - Euripides, Iphigenia in Tauris, Weiner, Main, 1977 October
  - Miller, Creation of the World, Hanley, Studio, 1977 November
  - Ionesco, Bald Soprano, Muir, Lab, 1977 December
  - Albee, American Dream, Muir, Lab, 1977 December
  - Brecht, Good Woman of Setzuan, Golden, Main, 1978 February
  - Genet, Maids, Burian, Lab, 1978 April
  - Anouilh, Thieves' Carnival, Leonard, Main, 1978 May
  - Devine, Amorous Flea, Golden, Lab ?, 1978 Summer
  - Hellman, Little Foxes, Golden, Lab ?, 1978 Summer
  - Brecht, Three Penny Opera, Hanley, Main, 1978 October
  - Guare, Landscape of the Body, Stelzer, Lab, 1978 December
  - Shange, Colored Girls, Barrett, Arena, 1979 February
  - Shakespeare, Richard II, Weiner, Lab, 1979 March
  - Alexander, Falling Apart, Asermely, Main, 1979 April
  - Shakespeare, Much Ado About Nothing, Milligan, Main (arena), 1979 Summer
  - Sweet, Hard Feelings, Gruenewald, Lab, 1979 Summer
  - Ridley, Ghost Train, Albrezzi, Studio, 1979 Summer
  - Miller, Crucible, Hanley, Main, 1979 October
  - Spewack, Boy Meets Girl, Milligan, Studio, 1979 November
  - Strindberg, Dream Play, Burian, Main, 1980 March
  - Allen, Play It Again Sam, Asermely, Arena, 1980 April
  - Beckett, Endgame, Bennett, Lab, 1980 May
  - Hamisohn, Dames at Sea, Barton, Lab, 1980 Summer
  - O'Neill, Ah, Wilderness, Golden, D., Studio, 1980 Summer
  - Shakespeare, Two Gentlemen of Verona, Asermely Main, 1980 October
  - Wilson, Night of Lanford Wilson, Hanley, Studio, 1980 November
  - Sartre, No Exit, Burian, Lab, 1981 February
  - Schwartz, Godspell, Bennett, Main, 1981 April
  - Moliere, Miser, Asermely, Studio, 1981 Summer
  - Moliere, Scapin, Schneider, Lab, 1981 Summer
  - Pirandello, Six Characters in Search of an Author, Jovanovich, Arena, 1981 October
  - Lorca, House of Bernarda Alba, Burian, Lab, 1981 December
  - Crowley, Boys In the Band, Bennett, Studio, 1982 February
  - Sondheim, A Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum, Jovanovich, Main, 1982 April
  - Shaffer, Equus, Leone, Lab, 1982 October
  - Euripides, Bacchae, Vasconcellos, Main, 1982 November
  - Norman, Getting Out, Hanley, Lab, 1983 February
  - Strindberg, Miss Julie, Burian, Arena, 1983 March
  - Goldsmith, She Stoops to Conquer, Bennett, Main, 1983 April
  - Mastrosimone, Woolgatherer, Bennett, Lab, 1983 Summer
  - Williams, Glass Menagerie, Leone, Lab, 1983 Summer
  - Wolfe, Look Homeward, Angel, Hanley, Main, 1983 November
  - Chekhov, Three Sisters, Burian, Lab, 1984 March
  - Christie, Mousetrap, Asermely, Main, 1984 April
  - Shakespeare, Anthology, Leone, Lab, 1984 Summer
  - Aeschylus, Eumenides, Valis, Main, 1984 October
  - Shaffer, Amadeus, Leone, Lab, 1984 November
  - Wilson, Fifth of July, Leone, Studio, 1985 March
  - Wilder, Our Town, Hanley, Main, 1985 April
  - Kopit, End of the World, Hanley, Lab, 1985 October
  - O'Neill, Great God Brown, Burian, Main, 1985 November
  - Merriam, Club, Valis, Studio, 1986 March
  - Shakespeare, Twelfth Night, Asermely, Main, 1986 April
  - Shepard, Buried Child, Burian, Studio, 1986 October
  - Deane, Dracula, Kelly, Main, 1986 November
  - Williams, Night of the Iguana, Asermely, Lab, 1987 February
  - Shakespeare, Taming of the Shrew, Leone, Main, 1987 April
  - Euripides, Medea, Valis, Lab, 1987 October
  - Simon, Biloxi Blues, Asermely, Main, 1987 November
  - Genet, Maids, Burian, Arena, 1987 December
  - Overmeyer, On the Verge, Brown, Lab, 1988 February
  - Marivaux, Double Inconstancy, Bennett, Studio, 1988 April
  - Shakespeare, Measure for Measure, Asermely, Main, 1988 October
  - O'Neill, Desire Under the Elms, Leone, Studio, 1988 November
  - Leonard, Diviners, Hanley, Lab, 1989 February
  - Cohan, Tavern, Morrison, Main, 1989 April
  - Norman, Night, Mother, Morrison, Lab, 1989 October
  - Moliere, Tartuffe, Asermely, Studio, 1989 November
  - Sophocles, Oedipus the King, Burian, Main, 1990 March
  - Greenberg, Eastern Standard, Brown, Lab, 1990 April
  - Howe, Approaching Zanzibar, Betts, Lab, 1990 October
  - Williams, Home, Scott Giles, Studio, 1990 November
  - Chekhov, Anton and Olga, Morrison, Arena, 1991 March
  - Gogot, Inspector General, Burian, Main, 1991 April
  - Beckett, Waiting for Godot, Burian, Arena, 1991 October
  - Sheridan, Rivals, Brown, Main, 1991 November
  - Jarry, Ube Cuckold, Bernt, Studio, 1992 February
  - Shakespeare, A Midsummer Night's Dream, Hanley, Main, 1992 April
  - Christie, The Unexpected Guest, Asermely, Main, 1992 October
  - Soyinka/trans, The Bacchae of Euripides, Giles, Arena, 1992 December
  - O'Morrison, Ladyhouse Blues, Fishel, Main, 1993 March
  - Orton, Loot, Dingman, Studio, 1993 April
  - Williams, Camino Real, Asermely, Arena, 1993 October
  - Wade, Key Exchange, Leone, Arena, 1993 November
  - Johnson, Brilliant Traces, Bernt, 1993 November
  - Hampton, Led Lisisons Dangereuses, Brown, Lab, 1993 December
  - Mowatt, Fashion, Lehman, Recital, 1994 March
  - Rivera, House of Ramon Iglesia, Giles, Studio, 1994 March
  - Shakespeare, As You Like It, Bush, Lab, 1994 April
  - Dietz, God's Country, Giles, Lab, 1994 October
  - Weill/Brecht, The Threepenny Opera, Bush, Main, 1994 December
  - Euripides, Trojan Women, Rivera, Arena, 1995 March
  - Shaw, Arms and the Man, Dalton, Studio, 1995 April
  - Vampire Lesbians of Sodom, Bush, Studio: Proposed Busch, 1995 October
  - Webster, The Duchess of Malfi, Brown, Lab, 1995 December
  - Wilson, The Piano Lesson, TBA, Studio, 1996 March
  - Shakespeare, Macbeth, Leone, Main, 1996 April